Preliminary Guide to the William Halal papers, 1980-2014 MS2227.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
William Halal papers
circa 1980-circa 2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Halal, William E.
MS2227.UA
37.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains material related to the career of GWU Prof. William Halal. The files contain materials concerning the courses he taught at GWU, as well as the books that he wrote and research that he performed. Also of interest are his files that document his participation in the World Future Society. The material dates from circa 1980 through circa 2014.
Biographical / Historical
William Halal, Professor Emeritus of Science, Technology, and Innovation at George Washington University, Washington, D.C. is an authority on emerging technology, strategic planning, knowledge, and institutional change, he has worked with General Motors, AT&T, SAIC, MCI, Blue Cross/Blue Shield, International Data Corporation, the DoD, the Asian Development Bank, foreign companies, and various government agencies. Bill recently substituted for Peter Drucker in giving a talk to 2000 managers at the Los Angeles Coliseum.
Halal's work has appeared in journals such as Nature/BioTechnology, California Management Review, Strategy & Business, Knowledge Management Review, Academy of Management Executive, Journal of Corporate Citizenship, and newspapers such as The New York Times, The Washington Post, Christian Science Monitor. He has written six books: The New Capitalism (Wiley, 1986), Internal Markets (Wiley, 1993), The New Management (Berrett-Koehler, 1996), The Infinite Resource (Jossey-Bass, 1998), 21st Century Economics (St. Martin's Press, 1999), and Technology's Promise (Palgrave Macmillan, 2008).
Halal is the founder of TechCast, a web-based system that pools the knowledge of experts to forecast breakthroughs in all technical fields - "A Virtual Think Tank Tracking the Technology Revolution." He also co-founded the Institute for Knowledge & Innovation as a collaborative effort between the GW School of Business and the School of Engineering.
Halal studied engineering, economics, and the social sciences at Purdue and Berkeley. From the website: http://www.billhalal.com/
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of William Halal, June 22, 2007 (2007.050) and May 28, 2014 (2014.011)
Arrangement
This collection is not processed and series have not yet been determined. For this reason the subject title assigned by the donor to each box (ex. publications) was added to the beginning of the original folder title. The boxes were kept in the order in which they were received therefore the box subjects are not in order.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material related to the career of GWU Prof. William Halal. The files contain materials concerning the courses he taught at GWU, as well as the books that he wrote and research that he performed. Also of interest are his files that document his participation in the World Future Society. The collection also includes material related to TechCast, a company founded by Halal. There are a number of documents related to presentations given at various conferences as well. The material dates from circa 1980 through circa 2014.
Note: This collection is not fully processed. It is available for use, but may require more additional research time to understand the order. Please contact Special Collections for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Technology; Faculty; Information technology
- Presentations - United States Department of National Intelligence, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Presentations - Institute for International Research - New York City, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Presentations - Planning Forum, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Presentations - Latin America (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Presentations - Small Motors & Motion Association (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Presentations - Institute for International Research, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Presentations - Litton, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Presentations - Sulphur Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Presentations - Israel/Passig (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Presentations - R.F. Weston, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Presentations - NTL Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Presentations - Strategic Leadership Forum, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Presentations - NSF/Susan Turnbull, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Presentations - Ackoff Center for the Advancement of System Approaches, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Presentations - Parsons, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Presentations - XPLOR, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Presentations - Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Presentations - SASE-London, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Presentations - World Association of Industrial and Technological Research Organizations, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Presentations - Department of Energy, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Presentations - AOLTalk, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Presentations - Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Presentations - Leon Fuerth, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Presentations - DC Chapter-World Future Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Presentations - Society for Socio-Economics, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Presentations - Biosphere Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Presentations - University of Kansas, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Presentations - Moscow, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Presentations - SAIC, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Presentations - Mercatus Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Presentations - Ethical Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Presentations - Arlington Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Presentations - Japan Textile Industry, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Presentations - International Quality & Productivity Center-Chicago, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Presentations - Credit Union Technology Research Consortium, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Presentations - World Future society, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Presentations - ComDex (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Presentations - Ackoff Conference, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Presentations - World Future Society, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Presentations - Consulting and Speaking, 2007-2014 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Presentations - Mexico City, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Presentations - Seminar and Book Signing, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Presentations - For Maddock Douglas Agency in Chicago, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Presentations - Ohio State, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Presentations - Army Emerging Technologies Seminar, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Presentations - National Academies, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Presentations - Committee on Forecasting Future Disruptive Technologies, 2008 May (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Presentations - Center for Strategic and International Studies (SIS) Workshop, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Presentations - Google + Hangout, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Presentation - International Conference on Intellectual Capital, Knowledge, Management and Organisational Learning (ICICK), 2013 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Presentations - Kogod School of Business, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Presentations - NASA Conference, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Presentations - Monterrey, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Presentations - Dupont Summit, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Presentations - Air Mobility, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Presentations - Bangkok/Singapore, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Presentations - Nato/Latvia, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Presentations - Singapore 2009 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Presentations - Singapore 2010 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Presentations - Singapore 2011 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Presentations - State Department, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Presentations - Association for Information and Image Management (AIIM), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Presentations - DC Council of Government, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Presentations - Boston, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Presentations - Langley, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Presentations - GW and DISA, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Presentations - Nato, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Presentations - London, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Presentations - American Marketing Association, 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Presentations - Colorado Tech University, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Presentations - Toronto, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Presentation - ULI Washington Breakfast Series, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Presentations - American Association of Cosmetology Schools (AACS) San Diego, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Presentations - Kaplan University, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Presentations - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), 2008 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Presentations/Projects - Enterprise of Future, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Memos, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Booz Allen-TechCast (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - 233 Teams, Fall 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Steve Roth/ECommerce, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Subscription ET, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - SAIC Teams, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Kristen, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Jossey-Bass, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Title, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Chiat/Day, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Pinchots, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Goldsmith, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - ALCOA, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Ackoff, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Koch, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Lufthansa, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - SAIC, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Telepad, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Novell, Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Lipnack and Stamps, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Miles, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Bell-Atlantic, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Walters, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Malone, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - MCI, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Cypress, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Hewlett Packard, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Dee Hock, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Book-Infinite Resource/Techcast Project - Conclusion, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
- World Future Society - WFS, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- World Future Society - WFS, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- World Future Society - WFS/Toronto, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- World Future Society - WORLD, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- World Future Society - WORLD Articles, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- World Future Society - Worldnet/India, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- World Future Society - [Loose Materials], undated (Box 3, Loose-material 1)
- World Future Society - World Future Society, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- World Future Society - Gottsman, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- World Future Society - [Loose Materials], undated (Box 3, Loose-material 2)
- World Future Society - Search, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- World Future Society - Development, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
- World Future Society - Institutional Reactions, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- World Future Society - 2013 Conference, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- World Future Society - Board, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- World Future Society - Index Etc., 2006-2009 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- World Future Society - 2008 Correspondence and Conference (Box 25, Folder 12)
- World Future Society - 2010 Correspondence and Newsletter (Box 25, Folder 13)
- World Future Society - Presentation in DC, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- World Future Society - Vancouver 2011 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- World Future Society - Toronto 2012 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Administration - Misc.-Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Administration - School of Business and Public Management, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Administration - Website, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Administration - School of Government and Business Administration Structure Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Administration - AACSB, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Administration - Election Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Administration - Mission Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Administration - SEAS-SBPM, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Administration - School of Government and Business Administraiont Planning Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Administration - Department Development, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Administration - SBA Administration, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Administration - Faculty Evaluation, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Administration - GWU, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Administration - Biostatistics Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Administration - University of California-D.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Administration - Leavey Award, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Administration - C.V./Bio., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Administration - University of California-DC, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Administration - UC Berkeley, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Administration - American U., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Administration - George Mason University, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Administration - San Francisco State, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Administration - University of Maryland University College (UMUC) Advisory Board, 2006-2008 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Research Projects - SAIC Project, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Research Projects - IKI, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Research Projects - Knowledge Management Roundtable, May 16, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Research Projects - General Services Administration, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Research Projects - On Screen, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Research Projects - CD-ROM/BDM, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Research Projects - CD-ROM Sponsors/Speakers, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Research Projects - Microsoft, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Research Projects - Redefining Corporation, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Research Projects - Corporate Community Article, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Research Projects - EOLSS-Globalization, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Research Projects - On The Horizon, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Research Projects - On The Horizon-Institutional Change, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Research Projects - Proposals, 1971-1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Publications - Science & Spirit, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Publications - Knowledge Management/SASE/Logic, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Publications - Emerald Handbook, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Publications - Evolution vs. Creationism, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Publications - Economic Times, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Publications - Democratic Corporation, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publications - Meditative Session, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Publications - Logic 5, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Publications - Post/Decentralization Strategy, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Publications - Third Way, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Publications - Computer Virus Op-Ed, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Publications - Hatchett, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Publications - Chapter-International Marketing, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Publications - Whites Only, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Publications - Futurist-TechCast, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Publications - Facing Freedom, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Publications - Organization Intelligence, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Publications - Dater, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Publications - Beyond Reagonomics/Business Crisis, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Publications - Great Crash of '87, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Publications - Writer's Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Publications - E-Commerce Article, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Publications - Technological Forecasting and Social Change, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Publications - Book with Soviet, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Publications - Information Technology Book (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Publications - Revisions of The New Capitalism, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Publications - Strategic Planning Book, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Publications - Knowledge Management Review, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Publications - Financial Crisis, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Publications - Through the Megacrisis, 2010-2012 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Publications - The Washington Post, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Publications - Correspondence with Enric Bas about publishing the book Technology's Promise in Spanish, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Publications - Space Policy Journal, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Publications - Global Mega Crisis (1/2), 2009-2013 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Publications - Global Mega Crisis (2/2), 2009-2013 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Publications - "Through the Megacrisis" Copy of and Correspondence Related To (1/2), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Publications - "Through the Megacrisis" Springwood Publishers (2/2), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Publications - "Through the Megacrisis" Rewrite, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Publications - "Through the Megacrisis" Chapter 3, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Publications - "Strategy and Technology" Copies of and Correspondence Related To, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Publications - "Technology Tsunami" Copies of and Correspondence Related To (1/2), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Publications - "Technology Tsunami" Copies of and Correspondence Related To (2/2), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Publications - Various Notes and Correspondence Related To, 2007-2011 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Publications - Breakthough Analysis Articles from TechCast Website (1/3), 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Publications - Breakthough Analysis Articles from TechCast Website (2/3), 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Publications - Breakthough Anaylsis Articles from TechCast Website, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Publications - Publisher Straight Arrow, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Publications - "Forecasting the Technology Revolution" Management Article, 2010-2012 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Publications - Article Reviews by Ken Harris, 2009-2011 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Publications - Publicist Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Publications - New York Times Op Ed Page, 1987-2009 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Publications - Futurist/So What?, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Publications - Christian Science Monitor Journal Collaboration, 2006-2009 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Publications - Shostak Book, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Writings - Morning Pages, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Rough Draft, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Various Notes and Correspondence About, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Next Book (1/2), 2005-2012 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Next Book (2/2), 2005-2012 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Preface, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 1 Intro, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 2 Energy and Environment, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 3, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 4 IT and E-Commerce, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 5 Media and Biogenetics, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 6 Transport, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 7 Space, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 8 Institutional Change, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 9 Consciousness, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Chapter 10 Scenarios, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Partial Draft #2, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Revised Manuscript (MS) #1 (1/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Revised Manuscript (MS) #1 (2/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Book Manuscript (1/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Book Manuscript (2/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Manuscript (MS) #3 (1/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Manuscript (MS) #3, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Manuscript (MS) #4 (1/2), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Manuscript (MS) #4 (2/2, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Notes and Correspondence About, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Editor's Copy, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Marketing, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Copy of Book, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Promotions (1/3), 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Promotions (2/3), 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Book - Technology's Promise - Promotions (3/3), 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Courses - Letters of Recommendations, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Courses - 201, Spring 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Courses - Management 233, Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Courses - 201, Fall 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Courses - 201, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Courses - Management 201, Fall 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Courses - 205/201, Fall 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Courses - 205, Spring 2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Courses - 233 Campus, Spring 2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Courses - 233, Fall 2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Courses - 233/SAIC, Spring 2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Courses - Emerging Technologies, Fall 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Courses - Institutional Change course, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Courses - 386, Fall 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Courses - WEMBA, 2012 Summer (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Courses - ISTM 233, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Courses - EMBA 6230, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Courses - Management Philosophy, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Courses - Organization and Environment/TNM, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Courses - Goals and Government, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Courses - Structure, Spring 2006 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Courses - Management 233 Emerging Technologies (Institutions), Spring 2007 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Courses - Speakers General, 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Courses - Directed Research Material, Spring 2007 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Courses - Exercises, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Courses - Evaluations, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Courses - Research Project, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Courses - Management 201 Exams, 1979-2006 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Courses - Management 233 Exams, 2002-2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Courses - Emerging Technologies Projects, n.d., undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Courses - Emerging Technologies 2010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Courses - Handouts, 1996-2012 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Courses - Speakers, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Courses - Scenarios, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Courses - Management 233 Emerging Technologies, 1982-2004 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Research Projects - S3, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Research Projects - Sloan, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Research Projects - EPA, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)